Peter Bates Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Peter Bates Papers.
undated, 1965-1973.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Bates, Peter.
.75 linear feet.
Student at Bates College (late 1960s) and one-time resident of Peabody, MA.
MSS19980196
Biography
Student at Bates College (late 1960s) and one-time resident of Peabody, MA.
Scope and Content
Carbon and photocopied copies of typescript novels, plays, poems, stories and other writings.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of literary materials. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Bates, Peter. Lindy.
Subjects:
Poets, American—20th century—Correspondence.; Short stories, American—20th century.; Plays—United States—20th century.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Manuscripts.
Occupations:
American poet.; Social Worker.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Provenance is unknown.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Papers, undated, 1965-1973
  - Black History Week—Lynn, MA, 1976 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Thesis on Dylan Thomas, undated (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Novel
    - “Lindy”, 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 4-5)
    - “Lindy” Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Plays
    - Untitled, 1973 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Two Children's Plays, 1973 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - “Kill the Condor”, 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - “Now or Later?”/”Bomb Scare”, 1972 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - “Peloria”, 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Poetry
    - First Drafts, 1964-1966 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - “Leaves of Dust: Poems”, 1966-1969 (Box 2:, Folder 13)
  - Short Stories
    - “The Adventures of Sydney Skeleton”, undated (Box 2:, Folder 14)
    - “Chase it”, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 15)
    - “He Never Means Well”, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 16)
    - “Let Him Burn”, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 17)
    - “October Ride”, 1968 (Box 2:, Folder 18)
    - “The Saucer Story”, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 19)